Why is everybody using
these tiny, little lights nowadays?
하나 물어보자
왜 요즘은 다들
조그만 전구를 쓸까?
예전엔 커다란 걸 썼는데
I remember when people used big ones.
재미있는 얘기네요, 할아버지
That's a good story, Grandpa.
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Wow. Monica's letting other people
help decorate her tree?
모니카 트리에 손을 대다니
누가 쟤 또 술 먹였냐?
Did someone get her
drunk again, or...?
크리스마스의 의미는
완벽한 트리가 아니라
Having a perfect tree is
not what Christmas is about.
It's about being with loved ones.
사랑하는 사람과
함께 하는 거지
멋지다
끝, 짜잔!
That is nice. And we're done.
Ta-da!
It just doesn't quite
feel like Christmas to me.
이유는 잘 모르겠지만
성탄절 분위기가 안 나는데?
Oh, here.
그래?
이제야 좀 성탄절 같네
See, now it feels like Christmas.
The One With The Routine
And that's the story of the dreidel.
이게 하누카 팽이에 얽힌 얘기야
크리스마스트리의 기원을
이집트로 보는 사람도 있는데
Some people trace the Christmas tree
to the Egyptians...
who'd bring palm branches into huts
on the shortest day of the year...
동지 때 싱싱한 종려 가지를
집안으로 들여오는 건
symbolizing life's
triumph over death.
죽음을 넘어선 삶을 의미하지
And that was, like, 4000 years ago.
4천 년 전부터 시작된 관습이야
네 얘기도 그때쯤
시작된 거 같다
Around the same time
that you started this story.
-Hey, you guys.
-Hey. What's up?
- 안녕 얘들아
- 조이, 어서 와라
I had to get out of the apartment.
Janine's stretching all over.
아파트에서 나와야겠다
재닌이 사방에서 스트레칭을 해
Everywhere I look she's like....
가는 데마다...
I can see why that's hard to resist.
왜 무시하기 힘든지 알겠다
난 재닌이 좋아
I like her so much.
재닌 생각은 다르다니 안됐다
I'm sorry she doesn't feel the same.
그러게
I know. And she's so sweet.
너무 사랑스러워
포도도 먹여주고
머리도 빗겨주고 싶은데
I just want to feed her grapes
and brush her hair.
You are aware that she's
not a monkey, right?
이건 알아둬라
재닌은 원숭이가 아냐
I am so over Janine.
난 재닌 깨끗이 포기했다
Yeah, at first I thought she was hot,
but now she's like old news.
처음에야 눈이 좀 돌아갔지만
이젠 봐도 심드렁해
-Hey, guys.
-Janine!
- 나 왔어요
- 재닌!
- 커피 하나 부탁해요
- 어서 와요
I'm gonna be a dancer on a TV special
for New Year's Eve.
새해특집방송에 나가
춤추게 됐어요
It's called some sort of
Dickin' Rockin' Dicky Eve.
그게 뭐라더라?
'디킨 로킨 디키 이브'
Hold it.
잠깐
Are you talking about
Dick Clark's New Year's Rockin' Eve?
딕 클라크의 새해맞이
특집 쇼 말이에요?
네, 그렇게 말했잖아요
Yeah, that's what I said.
Oh, my God, we love that show!
세상에, 우리 그 쇼
정말 좋아해요
어렸을 때부터
오빠랑 쭉 봤어요
Ross and I have been watching it
since I can remember.
아직도 네 안엔 그 뚱뚱한
소녀가 살고 있구나
You're still just a little
fat girl inside, aren't you?
I'm gonna be one of the party people.
올해는 나도 출연해요
파티 참가자로 뽑혔거든요
파티 참가자로 뽑혔어요?
그 친구들 끝내주게 흔드는데
You're gonna be a party person?
Those guys rock the most!
They said to bring someone.
Want to be my dance partner?
누굴 데려오라고 하는데
나랑 댄스파트너 할래요?
그거 좋죠, 재닌이랑
새해를 맞이하고 싶어요
I would love to spend
New Year's with you.
녹화는 내일 할 거래요
이유는 잘 모르겠지만
They're taping tomorrow.
I don't understand why..
왜 그러냐면
Well, how it works is...
the part with Dick Clark
in Times Square is actually live.
딕 클라크가 타임스퀘어에서
진행하는 건 실황이지만
But they tape some of the party stuff
ahead of time.
일부 파티 장면은
미리 찍어놓기 때문이죠
Not a lot of people know that.
이거 아는 사람 몇 안 될 걸?
Do you guys want to come too?
두 사람도 같이 갈래요?
-Are you serious?
-We are there!
진심이세요?
물어보나마나!
What are you laughing at?
뭐가 그렇게 우습냐?
난 쟤랑 이미 끝냈는데
넌 아직 얘랑 사귀잖아
Well, I used to date him,
but you're still going out with her.
Thanks.
Great, so we can all go together.
고마워요
좋아요, 그럼 다 함께 가요
가야겠네요, 나중에 봐요
I gotta run. I'll catch you later.
- 잘 가요
- 안녕, 재닌
Bye, Janine.
Did she just ask me out on a date?
방금 데이트 신청한 거지?
아닌 거 같은데?
I don't think so.
She invited him to the biggest
party of the millennium.
무슨 소리야, 새천년 최고의
파티에 조이를 초대했는데
하지만 너희도 초대했잖아
Yeah, but she also invited
you and Ross.
미안하지만 로맨틱한
의미는 없는 거 같다
I'm sorry, I don't think that
that was a romantic thing.
Well, maybe.
But, hey, I know how I can find out.
그럴지도 모르지
알아낼 방법이 있어
It's a New Year's Eve party.
이건 새해맞이 파티잖아
So at midnight, I can kiss her.
And if she kisses me back, great.
자정에 키스를 하는 거야
내 키스에 반응하면 옳다구나!
안 그래?
'이게 무슨 짓이에요?'
이렇게 나오면
If she says, "What are you doing?"
새해맞이라고 둘러대는 거지 뭐
I can say, "lt wasn't me,
it was New Year's."
That's better than Ross
kissing me in high school...
그래도 로스가 고등학교 때
나한테 키스해놓고
and saying that he did it
because he needed Chap Stick.
챕스틱 바르려고 그랬단
핑계보다 낫다
진짜 건조한 날이었어
It was a dry day.
우리가 딕 클라크의
신년 특집 쇼에 나가게 됐어
We are going to Dick Clark's
New Year's Rockin' Eve!
오 마이 갓!
Oh, my God!
나도 오 마이 갓이다
Okay, I've been on sets before...
잘 들어
난 세트 경험이 있으니까
시키는 대로 해
so let me give you some advice.
It's a show, but we're just dancing.
It's no big deal.
쇼는 쇼지만
우린 춤만 추는 거야
별거 아니라고
Important thing to remember:
Stay cool.
이걸 명심해
이성을 잃지 않는다
- 알았어
- 그래
-Got it.
-Okay.
Oh, my God!
It's just like I dreamed it!
맙소사, 내가 생각한 그대로야
자, 다들 모이세요
Everyone! Gather up!
-Excuse us!
- 좀 비켜주세요
- 실례합니다
잘 들으세요
The music's gonna start,
you're gonna dance...
음악이 시작되면 춤을 추는데
카메라를 쳐다보면 안 됩니다
we'll tape it. Don't look
at the camera. Questions?
질문 있나요?
네, 질문 있습니다
이거 언제 방송 타죠?
Yeah, I have a question.
When is this gonna air?
네
Yeah. Now, you guys dance
over there...
여러분은 저쪽에서 추고
여러분은 이쪽으로
두 사람은 여기 있어요
you guys, over there.
I want you two here.
나머지는 흩어져요
Everyone else, spread out.
우린 남매라서
같이 추기 곤란한데
We'd rather not dance together
because we're brother and sister.
네, 좀 이상하잖아요
Yeah, it would seem kind of weird.
여기까지 와서 그냥 집에
가는 것보다 이상할까요?
As weird as coming all the way down here
and then having to go home right now?
로스
So when is it gonna air?
언제 방송 탄대?
피비, 넌 주방을 살펴
난 벽장을 볼 테니까
You look in the kitchen,
I got the closet.
시간을 아끼세요, 아가씨들
나 여기 있으니까
I can save you time, ladies.
I'm right here.
그래, 넌 산보나 갔다 올래?
너랑은 상관없는 일이니까
Yeah. Why don't you take a walk?
This doesn't concern you.
모니카가 준비한
성탄절 선물 찾는 거야
We're looking for our presents
from Monica.
That's terrible.
뭐? 말도 안 돼
아냐, 매년 그랬어
No, we do it every year.
그럼 말이 좀 되는구만
Oh, well, that makes it not terrible.
Yeah, we never find them.
그래도 못 찾을 거야
She's always bested us,
that wily...minx.
늘 한 수 위거든
고 약삭빠른...
계집애
We'll search here for an hour...
걱정 마, 한 시간만 뒤지고
조이 네로 갈 거야, 됐지?
and then we'll go to Joey's
and search, okay?
아니, 되긴 뭐가 돼
어딜 뒤지겠다는 거야
-You can't look for Monica's presents.
-We have to.
찾아야 돼
You don't have to. And you can't,
because I live here too.
찾을 필요도 없고
찾을 수도 없어
나도 이 집 주인이니까
Well, then you should look with us.
그럼 너도 같이 찾아보자
Why?
왜?
Aren't you worried about
what to get Monica?
챈들러, 넌 모니카한테
뭘 줄지 걱정도 안 되니?
아니, 난 멋진 선물
벌써 생각해놨어
No, I have a great idea
for her present.
그러셔? 멋지기도 하겠다
Oh, that's it?
A great idea? Oh, yeah?
What if she gets you
a great present...
챈들러, 그게 아니지
모니카는 큰 선물, 중간 선물
조그만 선물까지 준비했는데
two mediums
and lots of little ones...
and you just get her one present?
She'll feel bad.
넌 큰 선물 하나만 준다면
걔가 얼마나 실망하겠어
Why would you do that to her?
Why? Why?
왜 그런 짓을 하니?
왜? 뭣 때문에?
-If I help, we can find them faster!
-Right!
나도 가세하면
더 빨리 찾겠지?
그럼
하나 찾은 거 같다
We have a live one!
-Oh, it's a Macy's bag!
-Yeah.
- 메이시 백화점 거야
- 그래
Who's it for?
오! 누구 거지?
"Dear losers, do you really think
I'd hide presents under the couch?
'바보들아, 내가 선물을
소파 밑에 숨길 것 같냐?'
P.S. Chandler,
I knew they'd break you."
'추신, 챈들러 너도
걔들 꼬임에 넘어갔지?'
Uh-oh. She may be onto us.
우리 음모를 알고 있는 게야
We are so gonna find them this year.
올해엔 꼭 찾아야 해
You said you'd go across the hall
and look. Do you do that every year?
아까 저 집에도 간다더니
매년 그런 건 아니지?
Yeah.
그랬어
You don't go into the back
of my closet...
내 옷장 뒤에까지 들어가서
가방 밑 같은 데도 봤다고?
and look under my gym bag
or anything?
-No. Never do that.
-No.
아냐, 그런 적 없어
That's where Joey gave me stuff
to store that I've never seen.
조이가 생전 처음 보는
괴상한 물건을 맡기잖아
Okay, that did not just happen.
그래, 없었던 일로 치자
Here comes a camera.
저기 카메라 또 온다
Right. No biggie. Stay loose.
그래, 긴장 풀고
자연스럽게
Why do they keep doing that?
너무하는 거 아냐?
We have to get up on one
of those platforms.
카메라에 잡히려면
무대로 올라가야겠어
They've been taping them all day.
저긴 항상 찍고 있잖아
좋았어
Right.
What'd you guys do
to get up on there?
이봐요, 어떡하면
거기 올라갈 수 있죠?
We learned how to dance.
우린 춤을 배웠거든요
When you learned to dance, did you
forget how to put on underpants?
그래요? 춤 배우느라
속옷 입는 건 까먹었어요?
Yeah!
그러게요
-Hey, you're a good dancer.
-Really?
꽤 잘 추는데요?
그래요?
엉덩이에 힘을 빼면
훨씬 좋겠어요
You'd be better if you
loosened your hips.
무슨 뜻이죠?
-What do you mean?
-Like this.
이렇게요
그렇죠
That's it. Feel the rhythm.
That's better.
리듬을 타요
바로 그거예요
좋아요, 댁은 저 여자랑 춰요
You're dancing with her.
아뇨, 그게 아니라...
-We're together.
-Yeah, we came together.
- 일행이에요
- 네, 같이 왔어요
I don't see it.
아닌 것 같은데요?
당신은 저 키 큰 남자하고 춰요
키 큰 남자 분, 손 흔들어보세요
You are dancing with the tall guy.
Tall guy, raise your hand!
Hey, buddy. Let me dance with her.
I like her, and I think I have a shot.
이봐요, 저 여자랑 추게 해줘요
좋아하는 여잔데 잘될 거 같아요
Really, you think so? I don't.
- 정말 그렇게 생각해요?
- 네
난 아니에요
I couldn't find anything..
Hey, wait!
조이 집은 깨끗해
뭐하는 거야?
Yeah, we found them.
우리가 찾아냈어
손님방 벽장
코트 뒤에 있더라
They were in the guest-room closet.
걱정할 거 없겠다
죄다 허접하니까
You have nothing to worry about
because they're crap.
Those are mine.
I got those for you.
그건 내가 준비한
너희들 선물이야
Oh. Thanks, Chandler, they're great!
고마워, 진짜 근사하다
이 괴상한 A하고 Z는 뭐니?
Chandler, what is this very weird
metal A-Z thing?
책버팀이잖아
멋진 선물이야
Those are bookends.
That's a great gift.
Oh. Okay, I'm sorry.
Thank you for my "az."
오, 그랬구나
버티는 데 잘 쓸게
원래 있던 자리에 잘 갖다 놔
Make sure you put all that stuff
back in the closet.
그래, 알았어
Yes, okay.
근데 넌 참 심성도 곱더라
이 집에 들어온 후에도
By the way, I think it's really nice
of you that even after you moved...
you still keep storing
that stuff for Joey.
조이가 맡긴 물건을
잘 보관하고 있다니
보세요, 댄싱 걸
Hey, dancing girl?
화장실 좀 다녀올게요
Can I go to the bathroom?
까짓 거 뭐
Here we go. Yeah.
거기 있어요
보기 좋다, 겔러 남매
Looking good, Gellers!
우리도 알아
We know!
봐
That snippy guy's the one who
decides who gets on the platform.
저 퉁명스런 사람이 무대에
올라갈 사람을 정하나 봐
- 옆에 가서 추자
- 좋아
-We should go dance by him.
-Okay.
Okay, everybody, hold!
잠깐 멈추세요
Next on the platforms are....
다음에 올라갈 사람은...
You two! And....
- 거기 두 사람
- 그렇지!
또...
그쪽 둘
-You two!
-Cool!
만세!
Excuse me, sir?
잠깐만요, 감독님
Would it help if I weren't
wearing underpants?
- 저도 속옷 벗으면 되나요?
- 모니카!
Monica!
Would it?
그럼 돼요?
How about me?
전 어때요?
이런, 키 큰 아저씨
Hey, tall guy!
함께 춤추는 그 여자 말인데요
I want to talk to you about that girl
you're dancing with.
괜찮죠?
She's nice, huh? To think I almost
brought my wife to this.
마누라 안 데려온 게 다행이지
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
네, 그렇군요
잘하셨어요
보세요
나랑 같이 온 여자예요
Look, I came with that girl, okay?
자정이 되는 순간에
키스할 생각이에요
I plan to kiss her
at the New Year's countdown.
오늘이 좋은 기회죠
그래서 말인데...
I'm trying to win her over. I..
꿈도 크시네
I don't think so.
그러지 말고 내 파트너랑 춰요
아주 흐물흐물해요
You can dance with my partner.
She's real mellow.
보쇼, 그 여자랑
사귀는 중이오?
Look, you dating this girl
you came with?
오늘밤에 잘되면
그럴 수도 있겠죠
I was hoping after tonight
that maybe I could....
그렇다면 임자 없는
여자구만 뭐
No. No. She's fair game
if you ask me. Sorry, buddy.
좋아요
All right. Hey.
맞아요, 임자가 없긴 없죠
사실이니 무슨 말을 하겠나요
Fair is fair. When you're right,
you're right. What can I say?
저런!
당신 초등학생이오?
Are you in second grade?
바지 적신 사람은 댁이야
Hey, man, you're the one
who wet his pants.
이봐, 그만해!
글쎄 모니카가 왜 여기다
선물을 숨기냐고
Monica would not
hide the presents down here.
No, but she did. Look, there's
that old hippie I've always wanted.
숨겼다니까, 내가 늘 꿈꾸던
히피 영감님도 계시잖아
혹시라도 여기 숨겼다면
건터가 모를 리 없지
If they are here,
Gunther knows about it.
내가 알아낼 수 있어
나한테 푹 빠졌으니까
And I could get it out of him.
He's had a huge crush on me.
That's not fair to play with his head,
though. You do it.
아냐, 그런 걸 이용할 순 없지
네가 해라, 레이첼
Okay.
알았어
Hey, Gunther.
저 왔어요, 건터
별일 없죠?
Hi.
Getting to be that holiday time again, huh?
또 명절이 돌아왔네요
그래, 기적처럼
Yes, it's like a miracle.
선물을 주고받는 때가
됐으니 말인데
I was thinking, since it's the time
of giving gifts...
여기 혹시 내 선물은 없나요?
I was wondering, are there any
presents around here for me?
무슨 뜻인지 알죠?
You know what I mean?
찾은 거 같다
-I think I found them.
-That's the Toys for Tots collection bin.
꼬마들 장난감 모으는 통이야
-That's awfully convenient, don't you think?
-For the tots it is.
딱 안성맞춤 아냐?
꼬마들한테는
-Hey, you guys, guess what.
-Did you find them?
얘들아, 어떡하니?
- 찾았어?
- 아니
No, Gunther fainted.
건터가 까무러쳤어
미치겠다
Man, this sucks.
엄마아빠한테 그렇게
자랑해놓고 방송 못 타면
If Mom and Dad don't see us
on TV after we made them jealous...
then who's gonna be
the losers then?
우린 푼수 되는 거야
야, 무대로 올라갈
방법이 생각났다
I know what'll get us up
on a platform.
What?
뭔데?
The routine!
늘 하던 거 있잖아
오빠, 그건 중학교 때 이후로
한 번도 안 해봤어
We haven't done the routine
since middle school.
저 무뚝새 아저씨가 그걸 보면
특설무대까지 세워줄 걸?
When the snippy guy
sees the routine...
he'll want to build us
our own platform.
Was it that good?
그게 될까?
남매 댄스 부문에서
감투상까지 받았잖아
We got honorable mention in the
brother/sister dance category!
이제 시간도 다 됐는데
다른 방법 있냐?
It's almost fake midnight.
Do we really have any other choice?
Okay, let's do it.
좋아, 해보자
Mom and Dad are gonna be so faced!
엄마아빠 확 찌그러졌다
다섯, 여섯, 일곱, 여덟
Five, six, seven, eight!
어떻습니까
So do we really need to ask who's
going up on the platform next?
다음엔 누가 올라갈지
꼭 물어봐야 할까요?
You get up there and do that
again, exactly like that.
아뇨, 두 분이 올라가서
똑같이 하시면 됩니다
됐다!
Get this. Dick will want
it for the Bloopers show.
이거 잘 찍어뒀다
NG 모음에 내보내자고
좋아, 컷!
All right, cut!
Listen up, everyone!
잘 들으세요
When we start again,
it'll be the countdown...
다음은 카운트다운 장면이니까
분위기 좀 띄워주세요
so I want to see
everybody's excitement!
Hey, guy!
너, 짜샤
3초안에 거기서 떨어져
You got three seconds to get away.
무슨 일이죠?
What's going on here?
저 바지 좀 보세요
Take a look at the guy's pants!
You told us to show excitement,
but don't you think he went overboard?
분위기 띄우라고 하셨지만
이건 약간 오버했잖아요?
What's the matter with you? Go!
이게 뭡니까, 당장 나가요!
가보셔, 오줌싸개
Yeah, take a hike, wet pants!
꿈만 같다
Can you believe this?
We're on the platform
for the millennial moment!
우리가 새천년을 기념하는
축하무대에 서게 되다니
누가 아니래
I know!
You haven't been practicing
the routine, have you?
오빠, 그 춤 연습
쭉 했던 건 아니지?
No.
아냐
나도!
Me too!
When the music starts...
음악이 시작되면
로봇댄스로 들어갈 참이야
I was thinking about maybe
going into the robot.
오빠
Ross, we should stick to the routine.
We don't want to look stupid.
푼수 되기 싫으면
하던 거나 잘해
자, 다시 갑니다
10초 전이에요
All right, we're back!
Ten seconds left.
-Ten.
-Nine, eight.
10, 9, 8, 7...
-Seven.
-Okay, it all comes down to this.
좋아, 결국 여기까지 왔군
Whatever happens, happens.
어떻게 되든 받아들이자
Destiny.
운명이시여
3, 2, 1...
three, two, one!
- 컷!
- 노우!
-Cut!
-No!
Year!
이어...
Happy "No" Year!
해피 노우 이어
Now we go to the live shot
of Times Square. That's a wrap!
자, 여기서부터는 타임스퀘어
실황입니다, 다들 수고했어요
What did that snippy guy say?
저 무뚝쟁이 아저씨가 뭐래?
I think he's kicking out
anyone who's not dancing.
춤 안 추는 애들 쫓아내나 봐
그니까 열심히 흔들어
So just keep dancing.
얘들아, 이거 봐라
Hey, look who I found.
안녕, 얘들아
Oh, hi, guys!
Birds have a very good
sense of direction.
새들은 방향감각이 뛰어나니까
우리 선물 찾는 데
도움이 될 거야
I thought maybe they could help us
find the presents.
Yes, if the presents are hidden
south for the winter.
선물들이 겨울을 맞아
남쪽에 숨었다면
아님 그 잘난 조크를 따라갈까?
짚이는 데 있어? 없을 걸? 그치?
Or we could just follow your clever
jokes. Any ideas? Didn't think so.
자, 선물을 찾아봐라
Come on, show us where
the presents are.
오리는 모니카가 쓰레기를
준비했다고 판단한 모양이군
The duck seems to think that
Monica got me garbage.
그렇담 나도 쓰레기만큼
훌륭한 걸 줘야 할 텐데
I wonder what I could get Monica
that's as good as garbage.
내 책버티미는 어때?
How about my "az"?
-Hey. This is hollow.
-What?
얘들아
- 여긴 비었어?
- 뭐?
안이 텅 비었어
왜 그걸 몰랐지?
This bench, it's hollow.
I can't believe I never knew that!
-Oh, the presents!
-Don't look directly at them!
- 악! 선물이다!
- 안 돼! 똑바로 쳐다보지 마!
What?
뭐?
All right, no, we could look at them.
좋아, 이제 봐도 돼
This one's for me!
이건 내 거야
이건 챈들러 거
This one's for Chandler. Here.
- 여기
- 좋았어
-And the big one's for me!
-Oh, let's open them!
제일 큰 건 내 거다
- 열어보자
- 그래, 그래
-Wait a minute. We can't do this.
-Why?
잠깐, 이러면 안 돼
왜?
난 별로 알고 싶지 않아
I don't want to know
what Monica got me.
이 선물 고르느라
고민 많이 했을 텐데
I'm sure she worked hard at getting it
and wanting to surprise me.
그걸 망칠 순 없어
And you guys are gonna ruin that.
We have to put these back.
This is not what Christmas is about.
제자리에 갖다 놓자
이러는 거 아냐
Whatever, Linus.
I'm opening mine.
어찌됐든 난 열어볼래
Nobody is opening anything, okay?
아무도 뜯어보지 마
I want to see the look on her face
when I give her my present.
너희들은 어떨지 몰라도
난 모니카가 기뻐하는
모습을 보고 싶고
I'm sure she wants to see the look
on my face when I get mine.
그건 모니카도
같은 심정일 거야
So, please, please, can we just...?
Can we put them back?
그러니까 제발 그냥...
도로 갖다 놓자
-Will you get us better gifts?
-Fine.
그럼 우리 선물 바꿔줄래?
알았어
나 왔다
Hey, guys.
You found the presents?
선물을 찾아낸 거야?
You let them find the presents?
챈들러, 너까지 합세해서?
미치겠네
Great.
내가 그 정수기 찾느라
얼마나 고생했는지 알아?
Do you know how long it took me
to find you that water purifier?
-That's what you got me?
-Yes, I see. That look is priceless.
그거였어?
무슨 뜻인지 알겠다
백만 불짜리 표정이야
Home sweet home, huh?
역시 집이 최고죠?
Nice to get back to reality.
현실로 돌아오니 좋군요
게다가 새해맞이도
미리 해버렸네요
Plus, we know how the New Year's
gonna go off.
I guess there's no reason for all
that Y2K panic, you know?
Y2K 때문에 법석 떨
필요도 없겠어요
그럼 잘 자요
Anyway, good night.
- 조이
- 네?
-Joey?
-Yeah?
Three...
3...
two, one.
2, 1...
Happy New Year.
새해 복 많이 받아요
What was that for?
이게 무슨 뜻이죠?
Tonight when they yelled "cut"
and we didn't get to kiss...
글쎄요, 마지막 순간에
키스를 못하게 됐을 때
I was really, really disappointed,
and I just....
정말 실망스러웠어요
그쪽이랑 꼭
키스하고 싶었거든요
I just really wanted to kiss you.
Really?
진짜요?
잠깐이었지만 나도 정말
키스하고 싶었어요, 아주 잠깐
In the moment, I really wanted
to kiss you too. In the moment.
-In the moment.
-But only in the moment.
- 아주 잠깐?
- 네, 그 순간에만
So do you want to kiss again?
그럼...
다시 해도 될까요?
Sure. New Year's Eve
is only two weeks away.
좋아요, 새해까진
2주 남았으니까
Can you wait?
- 기다릴 수 있죠?
- 아뇨
No.
Me neither.
나두요
3, 2...
Three, two....
You don't have to count down
every time we kiss.
키스할 때마다
카운트다운 할 필요는 없어요
알았어요
Oh. Okay.
Except I sort of felt like I needed
a couple seconds to get ready.
그래도...
마음의 준비를 하려면
시간이 필요할 듯해서
We were on the platform, ready to
dance into the new millennium...
무대에 올라가서 새천년을
기념하는 춤을 추려했더니
and the guy yells, "Cut!"
그 인간이 이러잖아, 컷!
조이도 재닌이랑
키스 못했겠네?
-So Joey didn't get to kiss Janine?
-Nope, he sure didn't.
할 수가 없었겠지요?
그럼 두 사람은 여전히
경쟁관계라는 뜻인가?
I guess that means
that you guys are still tied.
그럴 리가, 재닌도
우리 춤을 봤을 텐데
I don't know about that.
I think she saw us do our routine.
I may have boogied right into first place.
아마 선두로 올라섰을 걸?
So you guys are telling me
that you actually did...
잠깐, 그러니까...
거기서 중2 때 추던 춤을
실제로 선보였다 이거야?
the routine from eighth grade?
Yeah! But of course we had
to update it a little bit.
그래
물론 현대감각을 약간 가미했지
Hey, by the way, quick thinking
about catching me.
그리고 날 들어올린 건
멋진 임기응변이었어
There's no way you could've
done the end...
아무튼 예전처럼 마무리를
하는 건 거의 불가능하겠지
the way you guys did it back then.
What? We could do it.
뭐?
지금도 할 수 있어
I don't know. You were a lot bigger..
I mean, stronger back then.
글쎄, 넌 그때 엄청 컸으니까
아니, 튼튼했었잖아
I can do it, okay?
할 수 있다니까 왜 이래?
Come on, let's go! Come on.
시작해볼까? 어서
One, two, three, four...
하나, 둘, 셋, 넷
다섯, 여섯, 일곱, 여덟
five, six, seven, eight.
I can't do it!
못하겠다
Now, you do that, you're on TV.
그걸 했으면
분명 방송 탔다